对毒品  你是否抱着试试看的态度呢
Are you thinkin' about taking drugs?
三思  因为毒品并不是归宿
Well, think again, because drugs are not the answer.
看看我  汉克·维根
Take it from me, Hank Wiggen.
不记得这个傻瓜了吗
Oh, don't remember this ugly mug?
两年前  我还算是个明星
Two years ago, I was a star.
能连赢9场比赛
I won n-nine games in a row.
但八月底  我就离开了球场
But by the end of August, I was gone-
停  停
Cut! Cut!
不好  是吗
Not good, huh?
怎么说呢  球接的还不错
Well, you caught the ball.
听着  我通常不教人读台词
Look, I usually don't, you know, give line readings,
这次我来试试
but let me try this.
导演沉不住气了
Hollywood ain't holdin' its breath.
他们这套对汉克有点儿行不通
Yeah, well, they're doin' it wrong. I mean, for Hank.
去和导演谈谈啊
Tell the director.
我可不想刚结婚
I thought I'd give the marriage a few months
就变成唠唠叨叨的妻子
before I go for the meddling wife thing.
你们一恋爱  他的状态可就回来了
His arm came back the day after you hooked up.
去吧
I say meddle.
-你还好吗  -有点儿胀气
- You okay?   - Just gas.
去帮他吧  我正好调整一下
Go help your man. Give me a little room here to work it out.
看看我  汉克·维根
Take it from me, Hank Wiggen.
-这样行吗  -不太好
- Like that?  - No.
-亲爱的  -嗨
- Hey, sweetheart. - Hey.
-嗨  布莱恩  -嗨
-Hi, Bryan. -Hey.
是不是台词说不好
Having trouble with the big speech?
是啊  你有办法吗
Yeah. You got any ideas?
都是你亲身经历的啊  展现自我就好
It's your story. Just be yourself.
毒品摆在那里  你没抵挡住  就是这样
Drugs were there, you took 'em. Simple.
为什么戒毒呢
Why'd you get clean?
因为不戒我就完了
'Cause I was gonna die.
到了四月  你戒毒成功
And, come April, 'cause you're clean,
于是在对扬基队的首场比赛中亮相
you're starting Opening Day against the Yanks.
-这样来一遍?  -好
- Try it her way? - Yeah.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
先从第二部分开始吧
Let's start with the second part first.
让他进到最佳状态
That'll get him in the groove.
好
Okay.
我们先拍投球的镜头
We'll do the throwing thing first.
人人都想做导演
Everybody wants to direct.
-华纳还好吗  -还好
- Warner all right? - Yeah, he's good.
把你的故事说出来就好  亲爱的
You just bring it, babe. Just tell your story.
开摄像机
Roll cameras.
-开了  -声音  转上胶卷
- Rolling. - Sound. Speed.
加油  摆摆你对付扬基队的范儿
Come on, kid.! Show 'em what you're gonna give the Yankees!
好的  开拍
All right, action!
噢  天啊
Oh, God!
你还好吗  会没事的  会没事的
You okay? It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
他有骨质疏松
He's got osteopenia.
骨头太细了  不能手术修复臂骨的骨折
His bones are too thin to fix the arm problem.
不  只要有我想要的  钱不是问题
No. Price is not a problem if you have what I need.
-年轻人吧  -你怎么知道
- Young man? - How did you know?
如果是老年人
Well, if he's an old man,
骨质疏松早就是家常便饭了
osteopenia would just be a fact of life.
你会帮他减轻痛苦  打发他回家
You make him comfortable, send him home,
而不是在这烦我
which means you're just boring me.
他很年轻  骨质疏松很可能由癌症引起
So he's young, which means it's most likely caused by cancer.
你来找我是因为你没发现肿瘤
You're here because you haven't found it.
你有没有十分十分努力地找呢
Have you looked really, really hard?
核磁共振和PET扫描都没找到
M.R.I. And PET scan are both negative.
他几岁了  也许是早发性骨质疏松
Well, how old is he? Maybe the osteopenia is just early onset.
我来看看
Ah, let's see.
77年9月21日生的
"Born 9/21/77."
汉克·维根吗
It's Hank Wiggen?
他签了名  太棒了
And he signed it. Sweet.
"致医学界的赛·扬--杰米·威尔森"
"To Jimmy Wilson, the Cy Young of medicine."
-你让他写的吗  -就"杰米"两个字
- Did you ask for that?  - Just the "Jimmy" Part.
他的骨头太细  不能进行手术
The bone's too thin to support
不手术他就没法再投球了
the kind of surgery that would let him pitch again.
如果我们能找到骨质疏松的原因
But if we figure out what's causing the osteopenia,
解决骨骼的问题  就可以手术了
we can reverse the bone damage, then do the surgery.
然后打败扬基队
Beat the Yankees
拯救"自由世界"[打败霸权]
and save the free world.
昨晚是顿工作餐
It was a working dinner.
还是我们公司买单
My work- Company pays.
还真不知道  怎么就变成这样了
I don't know. I just feel kind of weird after what it turned into.
就是后来工作结束了呗
Well, then it stopped being work.
要是你有负罪感
You know, if it'll solve your ethics problem,
把这些给报了呗
you can reimburse me for these.
一共5.57美元
What are they, $5.57, I believe?
周五要是有空的话  告诉我
Mmm. Let me know about Friday?
-好  -嗯
- Yeah. - Mmm.
已经排除了常见病因
None of the usual suspects.
不是年龄问题  受伤前身体十分健康
Age isn't right, in apparent perfect health before this incident,
核磁共振和PET扫描都没发现肿瘤
M.R.I. And PET scan negative for tumors.
再做一遍  一定是肿瘤
Test him again. It's gotta be cancer.
抱歉来晚了  车在州际公路上抛锚了
Sorry I'm late. Car broke down on the interstate.
糊弄鬼呢  CHEM-7显示肾功能差
Don't believe you. CHEM-7 shows a poor kidney function.
为何20来岁的人肾功能那么差
Why would a guy in his 20s have a poor kidney function?
是癌症
Cancer.
先是骨骼  然后是肾脏
It first attacks the bones, and then the kidneys.
拜托  他17胜9负  防御率2.1
Come on, people. He was 17 and 7. His E.R.A. Was 2.1.
你主观希望是肾脏的问题
You want it to be his kidneys,
因为如果是  我们有机会治愈他
because if it's his kidneys, then maybe we can treat it, fix it.
但如果是癌症  他就再也不能投球了
And if it's cancer, then he'll never pitch again.
如果是一个普通人搬箱子时胳膊断了
If this were a regular guy came in who broke his arm lifting a box,
你会让他马上回家
you would've packed him up and sent him home.
天哪  圣人警句啊  我真是昏了头
My God, you're right. I lost my head.
忘了天赋人权了啊
All life is equally sacred.
我向你保证  下一个病人就算是针刺的小伤
I promise you. The next knitting injury that comes in here,
我也会一视同仁的好好治疗
we're on it like stink on cheese.
-他新秀年的时候175磅重  -停
- He weighed 175 his rookie year. - Stop.
在日本打了一年球  体重升到195磅
Now he's 195 after playing a year in Japan.
-为什么呢  -放浪形骸
- Why? - He let himself go.
是类固醇  我相信
Steroids. The guy was a drug user.
一个瘾君子不会犹豫用药来提升自己的竞技水平
I'm sure he wouldn't have balked at pumping up through chemicals.
可以解释体重增加和肾脏问题
That'd explain the weight gain and the kidney problems.
还有骨质疏松  去问问他在用什么药
And the bone loss. Go ask him what he's on.
死不承认的话  就采集他的尿样
When he says nothing, have him pee in a cup.
如果真是车坏了  会迟到一个小时
If your car breaks down, you're an hour late,
而不是两分钟
not two minutes.
用这样的理由来弥补两分钟的迟到
And two minutes isn't late enough
还真有点儿小才大用
to use a clever excuse like car trouble.
我本来是想早来的
I was coming in early. Huh.
说谎不打草稿  可不是什么好现象
Unprompted lies. That's a bad sign.
不是良心不安  就是有什么个人原因
Either a guilty conscience, or something personal's going on.
瞧  你只需要
See, that's all you had
进来  坐下  干活
to do- just walk in, sit down, do your job.
不  不  我从没吃过那些药
No. No, I never took 'em.
我们需要一份尿样
We're gonna need a urine sample.
不  你不相信我
Oh, no, you don't trust me.
宝贝  用吗啡没事吧
Baby, I'm worried about takin' this morphine.
只是止痛
You're in pain.
剂量是可控的  不能算再次失足
The doses are monitored. It's not a slip.
再说  你也不是对这类东西上瘾
Besides, opiates weren't your thing.
当年真该试试
They should've been. Whoa.
维根先生  我需要采集尿样
Mr. Wiggen? The urine sample.
要我说  不行  对  不行
I wanna say no, so I am- no.
信任是戒毒早期康复中的重要部分
Trust is a big issue in early recovery.
而且他的体重也增加了
He really did gain the weight honestly.
随便你说
If you say so.
你就是不相信
You're not gettin' it.
他觉得我是个白痴
He thinks I'm an idiot.
那的确
He sure does.
我们要保留些尿样吗
Should we save a sample?
"粉斯"[暗指豪斯]医生可会把它倒进玻璃瓶
Dr. Sports Fan can put it in Lucite
挂在脖子上
and hang it around his neck.
星期五晚上  你能帮我顶班吗
Hey, Friday night, can you cover for me?
应该行
I think so.
噢  星期五不行
Oh, Friday. No, I'm sorry.
抱歉  我要去参加肿瘤学研讨会
I have to go to that oncology thing, the seminar.
怎么了
What's goin' on?
我要和卡斯丁制药的药代吃饭
Dinner with the drug rep. Castine Pharmaceuticals.
阿尼吗  那个号称货存律师笑话500个
Arnie? Claims he has 500 lawyer jokes,
只讲一个的
only tells one?
不是  是新人
Uh... new guy.
要现金交易吗
You need cash?
不行  我身上没这么多
No, l- I don't have that much on me.
不  不  钱不是问题
No, no, it's not a problem.
我六点到  好
I'll be over by 6:00. Okay.
下午五点  豪斯医生离开
5 P.M. Dr. House checks out.
现在是4点45
It's 4:45.
我习惯四舍五入
I was rounding up.
凯洛·莫非特
Carol Moffatt.
请去第一诊室  豪斯医生主诊
Please see Dr. House in Exam One.
别这么快  凯西
Whoa, whoa, not so fast, Cathy.
我叫凯洛
It's Carol.
腿不舒服吧
Uh- Uh, trouble with the leg?
婚礼是什么时候
When's the wedding?
这周六
This Saturday.
噢  没多长时间减肥了
Ooh. Not much time to fit into that pretty dress.
更没时间买合脚的鞋子
And no time for practical shoe shopping.
每天跑两英里
You're running two miles a day
-过度疲劳了  -我这里疼
- further than you should be. - It hurts right here-
去买双新鞋子  少跑点儿路
New shoes, less miles,
不喝可乐  你就会是个美丽的新娘
and ix-nay on the afternoon Cokes. You're gonna look beautiful.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
我的隐形眼镜拿不出来了
I can't get my contact lenses out.
从哪里拿  你就没带
Out of what? They're not in your eyes.
但我眼睛很红
But they're red.
因为你在尝试拿掉你的角膜
That's because you're trying to remove your corneas.
你哪儿不舒服
What's wrong with you?
最近  我妻子说...
Uh, lately, my wife has noticed that-
说症状  没见我们正比赛吗
Yeah, yeah. Symptoms. We're working on a personal best here.
手脚麻木  便秘
U-Uh, numbness in my feet and hands, uh, constipation-
还有呢
And?
也许他不好意思在公众场合讨论私人问题
Maybe he doesn't feel comfortable talking about his private matters.
如果我总是小便失禁
Well, neither would I if I was having trouble
我也不好意思
controlling my pee-pee.
你是牙医  是氧化亚氮中毒
You're a dentist. Nitrous oxide poisoning.
你不是掉进了笑气瓶
Which means you're either dipping into your own supply
就是管道阀门坏了
or you got a bad valve in the office.
笑气戒毒治疗估计要比请个修理工贵
Laughing gas rehab's probably more expensive than the plumber.
还有  吃一点维生素B12
Meanwhile, get yourself some B-12.
还有人吗
Who's left?
我看不见了
I can't see.
不  开玩笑的  只是有点儿宿醉
No, I'm just screwin' with you. It's a hangover.
英语文学教授告诉我
My English lit prof told me
如果没有医生假条  他会给我不及格
he'd fail me next time if I didn't show up with a doctor's note.
和牙医交个朋友  让他给你写假条呗
Well, make friends with the dentist. He can give you a note,
再给你吸点儿氮气减轻宿醉
and maybe a little nitrous to take the edge off.
豪斯医生
Dr. House.
类固醇测试为阴性
He tested negative for steroids.
但β- 2蛋白有点儿高
Elevated beta-2 proteins though.
可能是癌症  淀粉样变性  或者淋巴瘤
Could be cancerous- amyloidosis or lymphoma.
或者类固醇  你们身上有钱吗
Or steroids. You guys got any money on you?
他类固醇测试呈阴性
He tested negative for steroids.
-我有几张20块  -有50张吗
- I have a couple 20s on me. - Fifty of'em?
福曼呢  脂肪垫活检和腹部CT扫描
Foreman? The fat-pad biopsy and abdominal C.T. scan
都没发现肿瘤  但是...
were negative for the cancers, but-
那说明只能是类固醇了
That just leaves us with steroids.
类固醇检测是阴性
He tested negative for steroids.
研究癌症治疗的生化学家挣的
Less money is made by biochemists working on a cure for cancer than
还没有绞尽脑汁帮他隐瞒使用兴奋剂的人多
by their colleagues struggling valiantly to find ways to hide steroid use.
但有一件事是他们隐瞒不了的
But there is one thing they can't hide.
嗨  我是豪斯医生
Hi. I'm Dr. House.
今天是我生命中最棒的一天
And this is the coolest day of my life.
看见了没  使用类固醇的人睾丸会变小
See? Steroid use shrinks the testicles.
我是清白的  老兄
I'm clean, man.
没用过类固醇  什么都没用过
No steroids, no nothin'.
你嘴上不承认  你的蛋蛋可没抗住
Your lips say no, your prunes say yes.
性腺机能减退  听说过这个词吗
Hypogonadism. Isn't that a great word?
谢了  这个词我们永远都说不够
Thanks. We don't get to say it nearly enough.
立刻给他用醋酸亮丙瑞
Start him on Lupron right away.
这些怪胎愿意为了娱乐大众来挣钱
These freaks are willing to defile themselves
而糟蹋自己的身体
for mass entertainment for money.
我真同情他们
I feel sorry for them.
尿检没问题  他确实没有服用类固醇
He drops a clean urine, denies using steroids.
现在你们又在给他用什么
And you're giving him a drug for what,
治疗类固醇滥用的药
steroid abuse?
不  不  不是的  是补钙的
No, no, it's not. It's got calcium in it.
对骨骼很有好处
It's very good for the bones.
基本上  从分子水平来讲
Basically, at a molecular level,
那只是牛奶
it's just milk.
惠特曼医生请到麻醉科
Dr. Whitman to Anesthesiology.
Dr. Whitman, Anesthesiology.
你猜卡迪多久会来找我
How long do you figure before I get a call from Cuddy?
你给他用醋酸亮丙瑞
You put him on Lupron?
-还告诉人家那药就像是杯牛奶  -是
- And you told them it was like milk. - Yes.
靠谱吗
Is there any way in which that is not a lie?
长得像牛奶
It's creamy.
-不过我有三个理由  -正当理由吗
- But I had three reasons. - Good ones?
一分钟后揭晓  我正在编
We'll see in a minute. I'm just making them up now.
他先对我撒谎的
He lied to me first.
你妈妈肯定教过你两个错加不出一个对来
Your mother did teach you two wrongs don't make a right.
他骗我说没有用类固醇
He lies to me about not taking steroids,
我骗他说那药不是针对类固醇的
and I lie to him about not treating steroids,
他被治好了
he's cured.
-帮我数着  -第二个理由
- Adds up for me. - Second reason.
如果我说实话  他就不会用那药了
If I told him the truth, he wouldn't have taken the stuff.
那如果他说的是实话
And if he told you the truth,
那药会对他有什么影响
what would the stuff do to him?
-严重呼吸问题  -第三个理由呢
- Severe respiratory problems. - Third reason?
消除安慰剂效应
I wanted to eliminate the placebo effect.
太棒了
Excellent.
你和你的律师可以准备打官司了
You and your lawyer can write a paper.
这点提醒了我第四个理由
Which brings me to my fourth reason.
我以为你说只有三个
I thought you said there were only three.
我以为你会买其中一个的账
I thought you'd buy one of'em.
认真地
Seriously?
他不会起诉的
He's not gonna sue.
因为他的律师是个好人
Because his lawyer is a nice guy
不会为了责怪我们
who'll realize it's unfair to blame us
而毁了这哥们儿一亿美金的身价
for ruining this kid's $100 million career.
好想法  不过不对
Good guess, but no.
如果醋酸亮丙瑞导致了呼吸问题
If the Lupron causes respiratory problems,
就说明他没有用过类固醇
it means he's not on steroids.
也就意味着他有其它的病症
Which means there's something else wrong with him.
而这个其它病
And the choices for that something else
基本都是非常糟糕的
are almost universally very bad.
骨质疏松  会严重影响他的骨骼
Osteopenia, messing his bones up.
性腺机能减退
Hypogonadism,
肝脏  肾脏功能受损
impaired liver function, kidney function.
我们可是找到了
And we have managed to find
全银河系唯一一个不用固醇类药物的
the only professional athlete in the galaxy
职业运动员啊
who is not on steroids.
不是癌症
And it's not cancer.
那是什么在摧毁他呢
So what's killing him?
有谁和我一样怀疑他的病是扬基队捣的鬼
Who shares my suspicions that the Yankees were somehow involved?
睾丸缩小说明他的身体不能合成足量睾酮
Shrunken testicles indicate his body's not putting out enough testosterone.
不考虑肺部问题的话
Throw out the lungs.
那是醋酸亮丙瑞导致的  我的错
That was the Lupron-my fault.
别担心  我会给他寄张不错的慰问卡
Don't worry. I'll send him a nice note.
环境因素呢
What about something environmental?
砷  汞  他的症状由
Arsenic, mercury. The symptoms could indicate
环境引起的可能相当小
Pretty small environment.
老婆没事儿  其他人没有生病的
Wife's fine, no one else is sick.
如果不考虑肾  其它症状都说得通
If you throw out the kidneys, everything else adds up.
睾丸  骨骼  肝脏功能损害
The testicles, the bones, the impaired liver function
全都可以由肾上腺功能减退引起
could all be caused by a breakdown of his adrenal glands.
艾迪生病  我喜欢
Addison's disease. I like it.
一般是这样没错  但是
Mainly, of course,
因为开始的治疗是针对
because the treatment is
-类固醇  -够讽刺了吧
- Steroids. - Enough irony for all of us.
治疗可以引起钠水潴留
Treatment would cause him to retain fluid.
再加上他的肾几乎已经不工作了
With the kidneys almost shut down already,
-他会死  -所以我们得给他换个新肾
- he'll die. - So we'll get him a new kidney.
你是说艾迪生病引发了
Your theory is that Addison's is causing all the symptoms
除了肾脏以外的所有的症状
except for the kidney problems.
什么引发了肾脏问题呢
What's causing the kidney problems?
卡梅隆
Cameron,
如果你有讽刺意味的猜想  最好趁早
if you had to make an ironic guess right about now
类固醇检查阴性
He tested negative for steroids.
同意  他现在是没用类固醇
Agreed. He's not on steroids now.
但如果他在过去的五年里用过的话
But if he was on them at any time in the last five years,
也可以引起肾脏损伤
it could have caused the kidney damage.
你知道  腰子不戴手表
You see, kidneys don't wear watches.
当然  胆囊戴  不过它戴了也没用
Sure, gall bladders do, but it doesn't matter,
因为肾不会看表
'cause kidneys can't tell time.
类固醇损害可以持续几年时间
Steroid damage could take years.
我还要说多少次  他没用过类固醇
No steroids. How many times does he have to tell you?
我不知道
I don't know.
在向联盟坦白可卡因的事之前
How many times did he lie about
他撒过多少次谎
cocaine before coming clean with the league?
那完全是两回事
That's completely different.
啊  对  我想起来了
Oh, that's right, I remember.
你压根儿没去坦白从宽
You never did come clean.
是联盟伪造血液测试把你揪出来了
The league was out to get you. They faked the blood tests.
你才给自己找了个律师才有后面这一出
You had to get yourself a lawyer and everything.
如果汉克说他从没用过类固醇
If Hank says he never used steroids,
那就没用过
that's the truth.
那太糟糕了
That's too bad,
因为我们的理论是肾损伤是由A引起的
because our theory is that the kidney damage is caused by "A",
其他所有症状都由B引起
and everything else is caused by "B."
这个理论的美好在于我们能治疗A和B
The beauty of this theory is that we can treat "A" And "B."
可如果你硬要把肾症状塞进去
But if you add the kidney symptoms back into the mix,
那我们面对的就是另一个字母了
then we are looking at another letter altogether,
字母表里可能还没这字母
one that is apparently not in the alphabet.
我就不能修复骨骼
We can't fix the bones,
而你将告别棒球  停止呼吸
no more baseball, no more breathing,
大脑歇菜
no more brain function.
找个别的解释
Get another explanation.
好的  内裤里倒是有一个  您要吗
Okay. I think I got one in my other pants.
等等
Hold on.
五年前  在缅因州的班戈
Five years ago. Bangor, Maine.
我的投球教练让我吃了点药
My pitching coach had me on something.
不过我一直不知道是什么
I never knew what it was.
你也没深究过
And you never tried too hard to find out either.
大概四周  我增重了十二磅肌肉
I gained twelve pounds of muscle in, like, four weeks.
对不起  亲爱的
I'm sorry, baby.
最近还好吧  医生
How ya doin', Doc?
好  非常好
Good. Very good.
你想让我把汉克·维根的名字
You want me to put Hank Wiggen
加进移植登记表里
on the transplant list.
他需要一个新肾
He needs a new kidney.
我想捐肾的人可能有货
I was thinking the kidney people might have some.
他们是要把肾留着给那些
They like to save them for people who have
我该怎么说呢  肾有问题的人
How do I put this? Kidney problems.
他是个职业球员
He's a professional ball player.
给大众带来了欢乐
Brings joy to millions.
你真想医院因为把他送回家等死而出名吗
Do you really want to be known as the hospital that sent him home to die?
您的好主意
That's a great idea.
可就让咱们成为双杀医院了
We could be the hospital that killed two people
那个本应肾移植的人
the guy who deserved the kidney,
还有我们甚至还不确定病因
and the ball player we bumped up the list
就贸然加进移植登记表的球员
when we weren't even sure what was wrong with him.
其他所有症状都和艾迪生病有关
Everything else is related to the Addison's.
艾迪生病检查结果还没定论
The test for Addison's was inconclusive.
艾迪生病检查结果永远是不确定的
The test for Addison's is always inconclusive.
那我们还做它干吗  问你不就得了
Why do we do it at all? We should just ask you.
你不会把他加在登记表上
You're not putting him on the list.
你真是比福尔摩斯还福尔摩斯
Your powers of deduction are breathtaking.
拒绝我能让你得到别样的快感
You take a perverse pleasure in turning me down.
就指望它活了
What I live for.
你要是想让老娘偶尔不爽的话
Once in a while, though, try to ruin my day
说点儿靠谱的
ask me something I can say "Yes" to.
啊  很抱歉  医生
Oh, I'm sorry, Doctor.
我不知道你在忙  我待会儿再来吗
I didn't know you were busy. Want me to come back?
-他在名单上吗  -没有
- Is he on the list? - No.
-把我的一个肾给他  -好的
- Then I'm giving him one of mine. - Okay.
怎么不劝我说是个坏主意
You're not gonna tell me it's a bad idea?
为什么要把肾给一个可能用不了的人呢
Why give a kidney to someone who might not be able to use it?
那不归我管
Not my area.
不过  那个可是我的椅子
That is, however, my chair.
什么时候手术
When do we do it?
真高尚
Very noble gesture.
我就好这一口
My favorite kind.
跌宕起伏  一无是处
Dramatic, yet completely empty.
异卵双胞胎移植匹配的概率
The chances of nonidentical twins being a match
-你一个人住吗  -你写书吗
- You live alone? - You writing a book?
我用问句只是想礼貌点
I made it a question just 'cause it's more polite.
你额头上写了个大大的"不得入内"
You got a big "Keep out" sign stapled on your forehead.
没错  早就说让他们挂在我门上来着
That explains it. I told 'em to put it on my door.
就算你不能像正常人一样交流
Even if real human contact is something you don't have
就算不想也不需要
or even want or need,
你至少应该能耳濡目染一点儿吧
you should at least be able to see it in other people.
是  没错
Yeah. Right.
现在器官移植确实是靠"真爱"配型的
True love- that's just how we match organs these days.
法国有对夫妇
There's a couple in France
高中时代就恋爱了  现在想交换大脑
high school sweethearts- they're trading brains.
我们会匹配的  测试吧
We're a match. Run your tests.
喂  实验室的电话  匹配吗
Hey. The lab call? Is she a match?
还没出来
Haven't heard yet.
不过你倒是有条留言
You got a text message, though.
星期五晚上  非常的隐秘
"Friday night." Very cryptic.
哇  谢了  能帮忙顶下吗
Gee, thanks for checking. Can you cover for me?
-肿瘤研讨会  -很好
- Oncology seminar. - Right.
星期五晚上和车在路上抛锚是一档子事吗
Friday night the same thing as the car trouble?
那时车真坏了
I had car trouble.
豪斯说你扯淡  我信他
House says you were lying. I believe him.
那是什么
What's that?
你鼻尖上有个湿乎乎的脏东西[说奇斯拍马屁]
You got a little wet smudge at the end of your nose.
嘿  挺喜欢他的
Hey, I like the guy.
想说就说  能做就做
He says what he wants, does what he wants.
他觉得能耍你的时候才和你说话
He won't talk to anyone unless he can jerk them around.
或者他想要一千元钞票  那有什么
Or needs a thousand bucks. What is with that?
我得分了
I scored.
美丽新世界  医生
It's a brave new world, Doc,
咱们就在风口浪尖
and we are the cutting edge.
你看到的是两张畅通无阻的通行证
You are looking at two all-access passes
直通天堂
to paradise itself.
-多少钱  -真正的价值  没人知道
- How much? - True cost? No man can say.
会计能透露下吗
Could that man's accountant say?
一千美元
One thousand dollars.
周五晚上
Friday night.
新泽西州史上最大的官方大脚赛车集会
The biggest official monster truck jam in the history of New Jersey.
你不是说周五晚上吧
please tell me you didn't just say Friday night.
无论已经计划了什么  取消吧
Whatever you've got, you cancel.
我不能
I can't do it.
听着  他们只把票给车主
Listen.They only give these tickets to owners.
无论什么时候只要我们想在赛道上
Anytime we wanna be in the middle of the track,
我们就能在赛道上
we're in the middle of the track.
这些票太棒了  一定要请假
These tickets are so good, we have to sign a release.
我认真的  为了这次  死都值了
I mean it. We do this, we could die.
要出席肿瘤讲座  我...
I've got the oncology thing. I...
直肠癌讲座
The rectal cancer lecture,
他们一年前就预约了  我没法脱身
they booked me a year ago. I... I... I can't get out.
实在脱不了身
There's no way out.
好吧  我找别的朋友去
Fine. I'll ask one of my other friends.
怎么  你觉得我就你一个朋友
What? You're saying I've only got one friend?
还有谁呢
And wh... who...
账房的凯文
Kevin in bookkeeping.
好吧  不过他貌似叫卡尔
Okay, well, first of all, his name's Carl.
但我叫他凯文
I call him Kevin.
密友俱乐部的昵称
It's his secret friendship club name.
-是个妓女  -哦  天哪
- It's hookers. - Oh, my God.!
很多妓女吧  但豪斯就是豪斯
Multiple hookers. But House is House.
这事他肯定有自己的一套  四或五个女人
He's gotta have it his way. Four or five women.
一点也不好笑
This isn't even funny.
什么  你不觉得他会和别人上床吗
What? You don't think he has sex?
当然不会  他
No, of course he...
他当然不和别人上床  他和别人嘿咻
He doesn't have sex, he makes love.
我可没那么说
I didn't say that.
化验室的电话
It's the lab.
福曼医生
Dr. Foreman.
呼吸治疗  请拨4702
Respiratory Therapy, call 4702.
呼吸治疗  请接4702
Respiratory Therapy, pick up 4702.
如果结果出来了
If you have the results,
我希望能同时告诉我们俩
I'd like you to talk to both of us.
如果还没  我得先去开个会
If you don't, I'm late for a meeting.
相信我  我更愿意和你的另一半谈谈
Believe me. I'd much rather be with your better half.
而那个另一半
And by better half,
我指的是那位把萨米·索沙三振出局的哥们
I mean the one who struck out Sammy Sosa on three pitches
那样还能省去很多废话
and talks a lot less.
但我觉得应该先和你单独谈谈
But I thought I would talk to you first and alone.
我从实验室里拿到了报告
I got your results back from the lab.
你们俩的肾非常匹配
You do match.
真的吗
I do?
你还怀孕了
You're also pregnant.
你不能作为捐赠者
You can't be a donor.
至少目前不行
Not in your current condition.
先失陪了
Excuse me.
我得去和我丈夫谈谈
I have to go talk to my husband.
心脏没问题  我们可以安排移植手术
Heart looks good. We can schedule the transplant.
不用移植了
No transplant.
罗拉不能流产
Lola's not gonna have an abortion.
事实上  你妻子刚让我
Actually, your wife just told me
为她安排一个流产手术
that she was making an appointment.
我不管她怎么说
I don't care what she said.
我觉得这事儿你们得先沟通好
I think you two need to discuss this further.
我们一直就想要个孩子
We've been trying to get pregnant almost since we met.
不管怎样  那都是你妻子的决定
Well, it's your wife's decision whether or not-
她想用孩子换一个肾  那是谋杀
She wants to trade a child for a kidney. That's murder.
我不会让她那么做的
I'm not gonna let her do that.
福曼说移植手术有困难
Foreman says we've got a problem about the transplant.
如果她为他流产的话
If she terminates the pregnancy,
他也应该不会自寻死路
he's not gonna let himself die on principle.
你会为了你爱的人放弃一个孩子吗
Would you give up a baby for someone you love?
你不是吧  非要我选的话
Please tell me I don't have to decide.
得看情况  看还能活多久
It depends. How long would they live?
对你来说这是个实际的问题吗
This is a pragmatic question for you?
能活五十年的话  我会
Fifty years, no problem.
六个月的话  就算了吧
Six months, I say let him die.
其实我在这个问题上思考过很久
I've actually given this a lot of thought.
我个人的底线是
My personal tipping point is
七年八个月零十四天
seven years, eight months and 14 days.
我办不到
I couldn't do it.
因为宗教信仰吗
You found religion?
必须是信教的人才相信胚胎是一条生命吗
Do you have to be religious to believe a fetus is a life?
似乎是有点儿联系
There seems to be a correlation.
我
I'm...
你喜欢大脚赛车吗
Do you like monster trucks?
-那是什么  -好吧
- I don't know what they are. - Right.
我有两张票  周五晚上的
I got two tickets. Friday night.
你在邀请我吗
You asking me to go with you?
当然  应该很好玩
Sure. Sounds good.
像约会那样
Like a date?
没错
Exactly.
只是...我俩不是去约会的
Except for the... the date part.
算了
Forget it.
不是  我本打算去参加一个肿瘤学会
No, l... I was gonna go to the oncology dinner.
当然了  你得去听威尔森的演讲
Of course. You have to hear Wilson's lecture.
不  他好像在两周前取消了演讲
No. I just found out he canceled, like, two weeks ago.
那么  我穿什么去
So... what do I wear?
-能听见吗  汉克  -对  还好
- Still with us, Hank? - Yeah. I'm here.
我胸口不舒服
My chest feels funny.
心动过速  你的心脏跳的太快了
Tachycardia. Your heart's beating too fast.
我们正在处理  你能挺住的  对吗
We're sorting it out. But you stay with us, all right?
说点什么  汉克  别停
Keep talking to us, Hank!
罗拉在哪里
Where's Lola?
注射10单位胰岛素  静脉推注吡嗪酰胺
Ten units of insulin sub-Q. An I.V. Push D-50.
为什么体内钾含量在上升
Why's his potassium up?
我怎么知道
Damned if I know.
再注射点降钾树脂
Kayexalate too.
我们得降低他体内的钾含量
We gotta suck that potassium out of him.
让心率慢下来
We gotta get his heart rate down.
-我们需要急救推车  -收到
- We need a crash cart! - You got it.
这绝对不是爱迪生病
It's definitely not Addison's.
也不是类固醇问题
It's not steroids either.
好了  请过来这里帮忙
Set. Help in here, please!
他的心跳达到了130而且继续飙升
His heart rate is 130 and rising
就像兰迪·约翰逊投的球一样快
like a Randy Johnson line drives.
你这比喻有亮点
"A" for effort.
现在给他移植毫无意义
There's no point in doing the transplant.
即使他的身体稳定了
Even if he was stable enough,
明显我们还未找出病因
it's obvious that we have no idea what's wrong with him.
刚开始心跳太快  现在又太慢
First it's too high. Now it's too low?
他的心脏对阿托品没有反应
His heart's not responding to the atropine.
-心率降到40  -我以为会升高呢
- Heart rate's down to 40. - I thought it was up.
现在降了  最低的时候心率只有35
Now it's down. Last time he went out at 35.
-怎么回事  -我不知道
- What's wrong? - I have no idea.
继续注射阿托品防止他的心率再降到35
Hit him with the atropine before he gets to 35 again.
已经注射了三毫升了
We've already given him three milliliters.
显然量还不够
Apparently that's not enough.
我们没法稳定他的心率
We can't stabilize his heart rate.
-你们做过什么  -降钾树脂
- What did you do to him? - Kayexalate.
他的脉搏太快了
His pulse was through the roof.
还有他体内钾含量也过高
So was his potassium.
不应该是这样的
It wouldn't do this.
肯定是哪儿出了问题
Something did.
等他稳定  或死了的时候通知我
Call me when he's stable. Or dead.
我还记得第一次见你
I remember the first time.
那场比赛本来不安排你投球的
You weren't even supposed to be pitching that day.
我长途跋涉飞到东京去看这个孩子
I'd flown all the way to Tokyo to watch this kid,
结果第一轮发球他就因为和教练争执挨了批评
and he gets tossed for arguing a call in the first inning.
啊  你投的球  太完美了
Ah, your pitches... perfect.
球速好像比你手臂的速度还快
Ball seemed to go faster than your arm.
球已经不按常理飞行
It was like the rules didn't apply,
势如破竹
like physics couldn't slow you down.
那简直是  太漂亮了
Hot damn, it was beautiful.
嗨  华纳
Hey, Warner.
嗨  孩子  你感觉怎样
Hey, kid. How ya feelin'?
我痛
I hurt.
手臂痛  头痛  全身都痛
My arm, my head, everywhere.
他们肯定调低了吗啡的量
They must've dialed down the morphine.
那是不对的  你正在遭受着折磨
That's just wrong, man. You're in pain.
我给你带了点儿东西
I got somethin' for ya.
不行
No.
这是其他医生给我的偏头痛药
A doc in St. Louis gave 'em to me for migraine.
我会上瘾的  我不能吃
I'm an addict. I can't take that.
罗拉也会同意用吗啡的
Even Lola was okay with the morphine.
这东西只是比吗啡强一点
This stuff's just a little stronger.
来吧
Come on.
我就吃一颗  华纳
I'll just try one, Warner.
马维尼医生  请拨分机6134号
Dr. Mulvaney, please call extension 6134.
又多了三个症状
Three more symptoms.
心动过速  心动过缓
Heart rate up. Heart rate down.
现在又出现幻觉
Now he's hallucinating.
你保证不告诉罗拉
You gotta promise not to tell Lola.
好吗  教练
Okay, coach?
他不是在做梦吧
He's not just dreaming?
没有快速眼动  他是醒着的
No R.E.M. He's actually awake.
-磕药了  -不像是迷幻反应
- Drugs? - Not psychedelics.
不然不会心律失常
Not with the heart symptoms.
幻觉有可能是洋地黄导致的
Well, hallucinations would point to digitalis.
也可以扰乱他的心律
It would also mess up his heart.
但并没给他这个药啊
But he's not on it,
他吃这个要干什么
And why would he take it?
是啊
Yeah.
精辟的分析
Pithy analysis.
终于明白为什么他们会请你做演讲了
I can see why they asked you to speak at the cancer dinner.
很遗憾我不能去参加
I'm sorry I'm gonna miss it.
很遗憾我不能陪你去看大脚赛车
I'm sorry about the monster trucks.
不  这很好  礼尚往来嘛
No, I think it's great. You're giving back.
但是  洋地黄
Only thing is... uh, digitalis,
只能解释新出现的症状
it would only explain the later symptoms,
而不能解释最开始的
not the original ones.
当然  你知道  这得做一连串动作
Sure, you know, it's got a lot of movement.
问题是  每个人都能看见这动作
Problem is, everybody sees the movement.
当你丢一个曲线球时
You're throwin' your curveball
动作就已经被别人看穿了
like you're-you're throwin' a curveball.
假动作  球行进路线一样的
Deception. That's the- same motion.
少做点动作  但不会泄露你的投球意图
Less movement, but it won't come back at you.
好了  外野手进来  到那边去
All right, outfielders move in.! Right there.!
你是怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
说西班牙语
Spoke Spanish.
告诉他们我是来从多米尼加来的游击手
Told them I was the new shortstop from the Dominican.
-汉克怎么样了  -很糟
- How's Hank doin'? - Lousy.
你的指甲周围都肿胀了  医学上叫杵状指
Around your fingernails, that swelling, it's called clubbing.
希波克拉底注意到他身边很多有这种症状的朋友
Hippocrates noticed that a lot of his friends
经常抓自己的胸口最后死去了
who also had that tended to frequently grab their chests and die.
对  我心脏是不太好  汉克到底怎么了
Yeah, I got a heart condition. What's wrong with Hank?
-你在吃什么  -洋地黄
- What do you take for it? - Digitalis.
身上有带吗
Got 'em with you?
奇怪了
Huh. Well, that's weird.
几天前还是满的
I just filled this prescription a couple days ago.
这里还有一瓶
There's another bottle here.
不用麻烦了
Don't bother.
汉克·维根偷了你的药
Hank Wiggen stole your pills.
他想自杀
He tried to kill himself.
到底怎么回事
So what happened?
他去喝水的时候把药瓶落下了
He left the bottle open while he went to get some water?
下一次把整瓶都吃掉吧
Next time, just take the whole bottle.
嘿  伙计  你没权利
Hey, man, you got no right.
人们能记得他们吃了多少
See, people remember how many they've got.
日期都写在标签上的
Date's right on the label,
正常人都能对药片的数量做简单的计算
number of pills- regular person can do the math.
但瘾君子就不必了
But a junkie doesn't have to,
因为他们关心的是还剩下几片
because how many pills he's got left, that's all he's thinking about.
为了大保单?
Big insurance policy?
-和钱无关  -对你而言不是
- This isn't about the money. - Not for you, no.
多数信誉良好的商店在你死后不会兑现你的支票
Most reputable stores won't cash your checks after you're dead.
但劳拉这样的女孩  她们只关心钱
But for Lola, well, girls like that, they're all about the money.
不许这么说
Don't you say that.
她曾救过我的命
She already saved my life.
在日本的时候我已经完了  是她救了我回来
I was dead in Japan. She brought me back.
从那以后都是意外之福
Everything since then, that's gravy.
我已经知足了
That's more than I deserve.
-你欠她吗  -我的全部
- You owe her?  - Everything.
那你的自杀未遂  把她吓得要死
Ah. So the attempted suicide, the scaring her to death-
算什么  感激吗
what is that? That's gratitude?
爱吗
Love?
我理解
Yeah, I get that.
忘了昨天你做了什么吧
Well, take out what you did to yourself yesterday
我们回来谈肾脏和骨骼
we're back to the kidneys and the bones.
我安排了移植
I'm scheduling the transplant.
永远不要拜访病人
Never visit a patient.
我要孩子
I want that baby!
就算我死了  是我和劳拉的结晶
Even if I'm gone, that's a piece of me and Lola...
自由呼吸  漫步街头
breathing, walking around town,
去看棒球
goin'to baseball games.
要是你  劳拉或别人  再谈移植
If there's any more transplant talk from you, Lola, or anybody else,
我可不会再搞砸了
I won't screw it up this time.
我一定会自我了结的
I'll take myself out for good.
我要开始对爱迪生病治疗了
I'll start treating the Addison's,
几乎会毁掉你剩下的肾脏
which will most likely destroy what's left of your kidneys.
行  开始吧
Fine. Start the treatment.
什么
What
汉克·维根在我身上撒尿
Hank Wiggen peed on me.
你觉得这条裤子在易贝上能卖多少
What do you think these pants are worth on eBay?
我办公室里有些大号尿布
I've got some big boy diapers in my office.
促销员像发糖似的散发
The rep hands 'em out like candy.
那么糟糕吗
Is it that bad?
不  要是你喜欢尿味的话
No, not if you like the smell of urine.
当然  我为什么要相信一个
Of course, why should I trust
对于周五晚上安排撒谎的人呢
someone who lies about what he's doing Friday night?
问题是  你到底周五晚上干什么
Question is, what are you really doing Friday night?
更确切的说
Or more to the point,
还有比大脚赛车更好的事吗
what could possibly be better than monster trucks?
或者说是我们分手了
Or are we breaking up?
史黛西这个周末过来
Stacy's coming into town this weekend.
我们一起晚餐
We're having dinner.
就是聊聊近况
Just catching up.
我肯定有条裤子在这里
I definitely had pants here.
等一下  史黛西是那个脱衣舞娘吗
Wait a second. Is that Stacy the stripper?
我听说她在大西洋城演出啊
I heard she's playing Atlantic City.
不是  是律师史黛西
No, Stacy the constitutional lawyer.
你觉得我接受不了这样的消息
You thought I couldn't handle this news.
你和她常联系吗
You talk to her a lot?
没有  有段时间没见了
No, it's been a long time.
要是你不想我见她
If you don't want me to see her
什么意思  我还是小孩吗  我没事
What is this, eighth grade? I'm fine.
要是你不高兴  可以理解
It's fine if you're upset.
不  是
No, it's-
我没理由不高兴
I have no right to be upset.
你们是朋友
You two were friends.
你该见见她的
You should see her.
替我问好
Say hi for me.
那么  你没事
So, you're okay?
我不是那个对癌症晚宴撒谎的癌症医生
I'm not the cancer doctor who's lying about the cancer dinner.
我不是那个背叛
I'm not the one betraying
所有可怜的没头发的快死的孩子的人
all those poor little bald-headed dying kids.
我得去搞条裤子  都发臭了
I'm gonna go get some pants. I stink.
你们虽然针对爱迪生病治疗
You're treating him for Addison's
却不认为会起效  是吗
and you don't think it's gonna work?
-他打算自杀  -我知道
- He tried to kill himself. - I know.
他糊涂了  我们可以再有孩子
He's confused. We can have another baby.
我会让他明白
I can make him understand that.
-我去流产  我们做移植手术  -不
- I'm having an abortion. We do the transplant - No.
我能对我的身体做主
I can make decisions about my body.
他也能对他的身体做主  他不要你的肾
And he can make decisions about his. He doesn't want your kidney.
他会死吗
So he'll die?
可能
Probably.
要是你去做流产  他也有可能死
If you keep that appointment, he'll also probably die.
保住孩子
Keep the baby.
你只是出于礼貌吗
Are you just being polite?
我的裤子
My pants are-
他们都湿了
Oh, they're all wet.
你闻不到吗
You can't smell that?
你认为她还是会去流产  逼他就范吗
You think she'll abort anyway, try to force his hand?
不  她不会冒失去他的危险
No, she's not gonna risk losing him.
好笑吗
That's funny?
不  豪斯请你去看大脚赛车  很好笑
No, the monster trucks. House asking you, that's- that's funny.
我是他第一个碰到的人  他就问我了
I was the first person he ran into. He just asked me.
对  像是个约会
Yeah, like a date.
没错  只是我们不是约会
Exactly. Except for the date part.
要是病人决定做透析
If the patient decides to go the dialysis route,
我们有些产品你可以看看
we've got some product you should check out.
福曼医生
Mmm. Hey, Dr. Foreman.
慷慨大方的莎伦
Courtesy of the generous Sharon
卡斯丁药业的好人们
and the good folks at Castine Pharmaceuticals.
我刚和他们说4月百慕大会议的事
I was just telling the guys about the Bermuda conference in April.
三天阳光潜水之旅和一个小时的讲座
Three days of sun and scuba, and one hour of lecture.
天  我们必须去听讲座吗
Oh, God, do we have to go to the lecture?
那么你就是阿尼第二咯
So, you're the new Arnie.
豪斯医生  幸会
Dr. House. It's good to see you.
能给我来杯咖啡吗  黑咖啡  不加糖
Would you get me a coffee? Black, no sugar.
行  那是谁
Okay, so who is it?
说吧  她和你们中的一个上床
Come on. She's sleeping with one of you.
老天  告诉我那个就是你
Oh, God, please tell me it's you.
她请客午饭  她不
She buys lunches. She doesn't-
别担心  你不是同性恋  爱冒险而已
Don't worry. You're not gay. You're adventurous.
你觉得她出卖自己吗
You think she's gonna prostitute herself?
我们三个对她那么重要吗
The three of us are that important to her?
恐怕不是  不
I'm afraid not, no.
歌迷和经纪人上床就为了接近歌星
The groupies sleep with the roadies in order to get to Mick.
你就是那个歌星吗
And you're Mick?
我打比方就是这个意思  没错
That was the metaphor I was making, yes.
你在这里干吗
Why are you here?
糟糕  原来是你
Damn, it's you.
不是爱迪生病  新症状  嗅觉丧失
It's not Addison's. New symptom. Inability to smell.
我刚才在汉克的房间
I was just in Hank's room.
他说闻着像老兵体育场的男厕所
He said it smelled like the men's room at Veteran's Stadium.
他没错
He was right.
我们排除了环境因素  因为太太很健康
We rejected environmental causes because the wife was healthy.
其实不是  过去6个月里  她丧失了嗅觉
Well, she's not. Last six months, she can't smell a thing.
要是把他俩看成一个病人
If you think of them as one single patient,
把她的症状放到他的身上
you add her symptoms to his-
镉中毒
Cadmium poisoning.
解释全部问题
It explains everything.
包括他们的怀孕困难
Even why they had so much trouble getting pregnant.
他们怎么可能接触到那么多的镉
How could they have gotten exposed to that much cadmium?
除非他们拿钢材和电池当早饭
Unless they were eating steel and batteries for breakfast.
哪里还有镉呢
So, where else is cadmium?
一些食品  被污染的地下水
Some foods, polluted groundwater.
我们该检查他们的住处
We should check their home.
我想我知道是怎么回事
I think I know how it happened.
我需要另一份尿液样本
I'm gonna need another urine sample.
-为什么  -当然可以
- What for? - Sure.
想要什么都行
Whatever you want.
你之前为什么不给  现在却没有问题了
Why wouldn't you give it to me before, but now it's no problem?
我要死了  不是吗
I'm dyin', right?
所以现在你没有顾虑了
So you've got nothing to lose this time.
正面回答我  你上次担心什么
Begs the question, what were you worried about last time?
有趣的是  之前我们检查的时候
The funny thing is, when we tested you before,
我们只是查了类固醇
we were just looking for steroids.
现在我们该查什么呢  汉克
What should we look for now, Hank?
汉克  怎么一回事
Hank, what's the story?
没人的时候  时不时来点大麻
A little weed every now and then when no one was looking?
我不信
I don't believe this.
-我们戒掉了  -你戒了
- We quit. - You did.
要是你继续
If you'd kept going,
你丧失的就不止是嗅觉了
you wouldn't have just lost your sense of smell.
我戒了烈性的
I quit the hard stuff.
我就是要放松一下
I just needed to relax.
基于症状  你不仅仅是偶尔用用
Based on the symptoms, you're a lot more than a social user.
-那么你一直在骗我吗  -对不起
- So you've been lying to me all this time? - I'm sorry.
大麻生长的土壤中一定含有镉
There must have been cadmium in the soil where the marijuana was grown.
有的人钙流失
Some people get bone loss,
肾脏衰竭  有的人睾丸萎缩
kidney failure, some people's testes shrink,
有的人嗅觉丧失
and some people lose their sense of smell.
我们马上开始治疗
We'll start treatment right away.
开赛时你会没事的
You should be fine by opening day.
棒球在夏天  对吗
Baseball's in the summer, right?
不会影响到婴儿  会吗  镉
It didn't hurt the baby, did it? The cadmium?
要是你完全戒了  婴儿应该没事
If you've been clean, the baby should be fine.
好的
Okay.
求你了  我会都戒了的
Please. I'll stop everything.
我会  我每天去戒毒互助会
I'll- I'll go to meetings every day.
罗拉
Lola.
每天两次
Twice a day.
棒球手怎样了
How's the ballplayer doing?
-好多了  -他职业生涯就惨了
- Much better. - Too bad about his career.
什么意思
What do you mean?
棒球联盟劳资谈判决定
Major League Baseball's collective bargaining agreement...
要求提供全部医疗就诊记录
requires medical reports on all treatment.
鉴于汉克的记录  不可能宽大处理
Given Hank's history, he's not likely to get much leniency.
他们为何要介意他有过爱迪生病的治疗呢
Why should they care that he's being treated for Addison's?
我们没有做爱迪生病治疗
You're not treating him for Addison's.
报告是这么写的
My report says I am.
你竟敢编报告?
You're lying on the report?
人人都会犯傻
Well, everybody does stupid things.
不该因此剥夺他们全部的生活
It shouldn't cost them everything they want in life.
是不应该  不过通常都会
No, it shouldn't, but it usually does.
话说回来  除非是能打败扬基队
On the other hand, if it means someone can actually beat the Yankees-
豪斯  怎么说  有办法让他参加吗
So what about House? Is there any way we can get him down there?
你非要谈工作吗
You really wanna talk about work?
不  一点不
No. Not at all.
不可思议啊
That was amazing!
我告诉你  掘墓人队从来不会让你失望
I'm telling you. Grave Digger never disappoints.
你结过婚吗
You ever been married?
现在
Well, now,
别谈私人问题  毁了美好的夜晚
let's not ruin a lovely night out by getting personal.
我和某人同居了段时间
I lived with someone for a while.
你要吃完吗
You gonna finish that?
看谁先跑到车那里
I'll race you to the car.